<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <gameList>
   <game>
     <path>./berzerk.tap</path>
     <name>Berzerk</name>
     <desc>Navigate the play field avoiding all robots.  Take too long and a smiler will come to trance on you! Shoot the enemies if you wish.  Enemies will always track towards you. Avoid wall at all costs. Follow direction of arrow to try to escape the maze. Enemies will fire back after a few moves, and will gradually get more aggressive. End sequence if you escape, not just a simple well done message.... Use keys Q,A,O,P and space to move and fire.</desc>
     <image>./berzerk.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170616T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Bootlegger</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Berzerk</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
    <game>
     <path>./breakspace.tap</path>
     <name>Break/Space</name>
     <desc>Break/Space is a procedurally-generated space strategy game for the 48K ZX Spectrum. After an accident while testing an experimental warp drive, you find yourself stranded in an uncharted area of the universe. Your only chance of getting home is to recover  your four warp cores (jettisoned during the accident) and then return to the wormhole  that brought you here in order to get back to warp speed and back to Earth. Unfortunately this part of the universe is inhabited by six alien races - some nice,  some not-so-nice. You can barter and battle with these as you see fit, although be  careful - your actions will have consequences, and beating up an easy mark can make  them less likely to deal with you the next time your paths cross. Complicating matters more is the fact that your long-range scanners are broken so you  can't see what's ahead of you until you enter a region. Your ship is also a little underpowered and can only carry a certain amount of fuel and armaments. However, it's possible to use the few supplies you have to earn money, which you can then use to replenish stocks or improve your ship. And out in the darkness of space, perhaps there are other opportunities awaiting you? But don't take too long. The wormhole will close soon, and once that happens you'll be trapped here forever!</desc>
     <image>./breakspace.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170912T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Blerkotron</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Break/Space 1.9</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./cadaverion.tap</path>
     <name>Cadaverion</name>
     <desc>Help Cheril in the sixth game in the Cheril Trilogy! You have approximately one minute to escape each of the four floors in the mansion, each floor being composed by five closed chambers. To progress from one chamber to the next, you'll have to open the gate by means of pushing around every statue on the screen to their bases. If you get it wrong you can always restart the room by pressing "fire" over the blueish tile you will find in every room with statues. This will revert the room to the original position. You must hurry, because if the time runs out you'll have to start the current floor over. Luckily, you can collect hourglasses for some more time, but be careful with the mansion inhabitants, who are everything but friendly.</desc>
     <image>./cadaverion.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20131014T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Cadaverion</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./cherilofthebosque.tzx</path>
     <name>Cheril of the Bosque</name>
     <desc>Control Cheril accross the jungle looking for giant nuts. When you manage to collect thirteen of them, the game will end and you'll win. In already visited screens, a tasteful roasted chicken may appear, and it will help you to recover some life points, which you'll lose when you hit an enemy, a ball of spikes, poisonous shrooms or carnivorous plants.</desc>
     <image>./cherilofthebosque.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20100201T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Cheril of the Bosque</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./cherilperils.tzx</path>
     <name>Cheril Perils</name>
     <desc>Control Cheril in the doomed city of Yellowenia, infested with zombies. Your mission is relatively easy to understand: smash 60 zombies using the method of busting them jumping on their fragile skulls. When you can see them coming, just drop on them! Jump on them! KILL'EM ALL! When you have slain all the 60 zombies, the mayor will remove the boulders which block the exit, in the very first screen of the game. So when you are done, just leave. Good luck!</desc>
     <image>./cherilperils.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20100701T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Cheril Perils</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./cherilthegoddess.tap</path>
     <name>Cheril the Goddess</name>
     <desc>You control Cheril. There's plenty of things to do, and you'll need special objects. Cheril can only carry ONE object at a time, so if you try to get a new one while you are carring an object, you will drop the one you carry in the place of the one you take. To get/interchange objects press DOWN. Besides, you'll have to give those objects a use. To use an object, just walk to the place you want to use it and press DOWN. For Cheril to fly, she has to "push". You can make her "push" by pressing UP. But beware: "pushing" for too long drains Cheril's vitality, so you have to do this carefully. Timing short "pushes" can make her gain momentum. Take your time to master the technique, it won't take long. Cheril can also fire power balls. You can fire pressing FIRE. Power balls also drain Cheril, but think that enemies do quite a lot of harm. Use this feature wisely, and just when needed! Cheril can also regain her vitality by means of a special action we won't reveal 'cause it's easy enough to find out! You can choose the difficulty level, but the easiest level won't show the real ending.</desc>
     <image>./cherilthegoddess.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20121201T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Cheril the Goddess [v.2.0]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./columns.tzx</path>
     <name>Columns</name>
     <desc>There are two ways to play Columns. On the one hand there is the traditional one that is very simple, remove the maximum number of stones before the time reaches zero or that you fill the screen of stones and die crushed. The second way to play is by levels: It turns out that one day, a little princess was cloistered on top of a pyramid for a handsome Prince Charming to save her and take her in marriage (if necessary, of course). As in the beautiful traditional stories, we have to rescue the princess dam in the pyramid. To get to it we have to go advancing rooms. Each room is a level and the closer we are the more difficult it will be for us to pass because the stones that we will have to remove will be more and more, they will fall faster and the time decreasing. But not everything is bad news, every time we move from room we get 10 extra seconds and each time we remove stones in quantity greater than three, we also get extra time. The more stones of a stroke, the more points.</desc>
     <image>./columns.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20090101T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Columns ZX</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./elhobbit.tzx</path>
     <name>El Hobbit (Vah-ka's Cut)</name>
     <desc>Bilbo is a Hobbit, which is somehow like that small and skinny guy you remember from school which could run very fast. One nice day he was relaxing at home and got a call from Gandalf, an odd old chap who worked as a magician (in the good ol' Merlin fashion) and as the gay professor in Harry Potter. The old man tells you about a big treasure hidden in a cave and guarded by Smaug, the terrible pink dragon - the problem being that he doesn't really know how to open the cave to get it. That's something which only the thirteen dwarves (dirty short people with long beards) know how to do; they usually wander around the forest. Besides, inside the cave there's a bald grumpy man called Gollum who has hidden a ring somewhere. That ring is rather special, cause if you put it on you become invisible (thus unkillable by enemies) but feel a bit dizzy. In The Hobbit (Vahka's cut) your mission is to help Bilbo find Smaug's treasure without dying in the attempt. To do so, you will have to perform some tasks (hints already given). To move around you use your OPQA keys or the joystick. To talk to people / examine stuff / pick up stuff, etcetera, just press SPACE of FIRE in the joystick. When you get the ring (hint, hint!) you can put it on by pressing SPACE / FIRE as well. Beware, the effects are short and you will get a bit dizzy. You will need this cause Gollums dwells in very thin corridors and you won't be able to get past him without being invisible.</desc>
     <image>./elhobbit.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20130103T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>El Hobbit (Vah-ka's Cut)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./gokumal.tap</path>
     <name>Goku Mal</name>
     <desc>Help Goku Bad finding Eleuterio to beat the crap out of him. You'll have to traverse five stages full of hideous creatures, starting in the secret labs, getting past the sewers, going accross the broken bridge, stopping in a church to pick up some flowers, and finally descending the industrial zone to its very bottoms, where Eleuterio dwells. Dispose of all those disgusting monsters firing your balls of power and try not to fall in the spikes or touching the radioactive snot in the sewers.</desc>
     <image>./gokumal.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20131101T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Goku Mal</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./horacegoestotower.tzx</path>
     <name>Horace Goes To The Tower</name>
     <desc>The game is simple: jump and run, find keys to fit in keyholes and open your path to unaccesible areas, and get all the master tapes (10 in total) spread accross the whole tower. In many screens, in order to be able to advance, you'll have to push special blocks (checkered and green) to move them to most adecuate places so you can jump on them and reach higher platforms you wouldn't otherwise reach. If you get trapped, thanks to the miracles of modern science, you can press R so everything gets back to its original place (you included).</desc>
     <image>./horacegoestotower.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20110801T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Horace Goes To The Tower</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./inkfall.z80</path>
     <name>Ink Fall</name>
     <desc>Simple puzzle game. Choose an ink colour from palette on the right. Use QA, OP, 67 to move cursor, and Space or 0 to action. Ink will fill from left to right and top to bottom. Try to fill whole page in one colour. Be sure to choose a colour before the time runs out. Once colour is actioned, all adjacent same colours will fill with new colour.  When a different colour is hit, the fill will stop. You can not use the last chosen colour on your next go (last colour is highlighted and will be skipped over on cursor move). Try to complete in the lowest amount of move to gain a Lo-Score.</desc>
     <image>./inkfall.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170620T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Bootlegger</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Ink Fall [after compo version]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./judgevsbaldo.tzx</path>
     <name>Judge Morry vs. Baldo Midget</name>
     <desc>It is a game for two players, and it is about charging the opponent before the opponent is charged to you.  Easy and simple. And then you'll complain that your neurons are dying and things like that.  That I have told you. So much wine, and then hangover ... Of course your head hurts!  Controls: Player 1: Judge Morry; Q-left; W-right; E-shot; R-jump; Player 2: Baldo Midget; U-left; I-right; O-shot; P-jump.</desc>
     <image>./judgevsbaldo.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20071231T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Judge Morry vs. Baldo Midget</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./lalaprologue.tzx</path>
     <name>Lala Prologue</name>
     <desc>Take control of Lala accross the decrepit surroundings of Morgana's academy, looking for all her filters and chemicals.  To progress in your adventure you have to fetch and use some keys which will open a series of gates, giving you access to new areas. Avoid the flying nasties and spike traps around the cementary and the churches around, which can be really fatal. To regain some life, you can eat heart-shaped lollipops which will lay scattered here and there and which will appear once you've collected some filters and formulae, in screens already visited. Controls: O: Left; P: Right; Q/SPACE: Jump.</desc>
     <image>./lalaprologue.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20100126T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Lala Prologue</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>leovigildo1.tap</path>
     <name>Leovigildo (part 1)</name>
     <desc>The game is divided into 4 different blocks. The first chapter has four different endings, depending on the tasks you complete before talking to the Duchess. Only one of those endings is the real one (according to the story). You can get and carry boxes pressing DOWN, and drop them elsewhere pressing DOWN again. In every chapter you can use DOWN to get, examine, talk or use an object. You can manage your inventory pressing Z to change the cursor which points to the active slot to select which object you want to use / in which slot you want to store a new object. You can use two different keyboard configurations (WSADNM, QAOPM), Joystick Sinclair or Joystick Kempston. These are the key bindings, first for the WSADNM configuration, the the OPQAM configuration, then the Joystics. Controls: A, O, Left: go left; D, P, Right: go right.; S, A, Down: use object, examine, talk, get box, drop box.; N, Q, Up: jump.; M, Fire: Throw box (chapter 2); Z: select slot in the inventory; H: Pause; Y: Exit to title.</desc>
     <image>./leovigildo1.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20141103T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Leovigildo (part 1)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>leovigildo2.tap</path>
     <name>Leovigildo (part 2)</name>
     <desc>The game is divided into 4 different blocks. On the second chapter, you have to kill all the enemies on the screen before you progress to the next. If you run out of boxes, you can restart the level stepping on the special tile and pressing down - but you'll lose a life. You can get and carry boxes pressing DOWN, and drop them elsewhere pressing DOWN again. In the second chapter, besides, you can throw such boxes to kill enemies, pressing FIRE. In every chapter you can use DOWN to get, examine, talk or use an object. You can manage your inventory pressing Z to change the cursor which points to the active slot to select which object you want to use / in which slot you want to store a new object. You can use two different keyboard configurations (WSADNM, QAOPM), Joystick Sinclair or Joystick Kempston. These are the key bindings, first for the WSADNM configuration, the the OPQAM configuration, then the Joystics. Controls: A, O, Left: go left; D, P, Right: go right.; S, A, Down: use object, examine, talk, get box, drop box.; N, Q, Up: jump.; M, Fire: Throw box (chapter 2); Z: select slot in the inventory; H: Pause; Y: Exit to title.</desc>
     <image>./leovigildo2.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20141103T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Leovigildo (part 2)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>leovigildo3.tap</path>
     <name>Leovigildo (part 3)</name>
     <desc>The game is divided into 4 different blocks. On the third chapter, you control the duchess, who can jump over trampoline boxes to reach higher. You can also transport such boxes, but they are so heavy that they will deplete your energy. You can get and carry boxes pressing DOWN, and drop them elsewhere pressing DOWN again. In the third chapter, you can jump over boxes which have became trampolines of sorts which you can also carry around, but they are so heavy that will deplete your energy. In every chapter you can use DOWN to get, examine, talk or use an object. You can manage your inventory pressing Z to change the cursor which points to the active slot to select which object you want to use / in which slot you want to store a new object. You can use two different keyboard configurations (WSADNM, QAOPM), Joystick Sinclair or Joystick Kempston. These are the key bindings, first for the WSADNM configuration, the the OPQAM configuration, then the Joystics. Controls: A, O, Left: go left; D, P, Right: go right.; S, A, Down: use object, examine, talk, get box, drop box.; N, Q, Up: jump.; M, Fire: Throw box (chapter 2); Z: select slot in the inventory; H: Pause; Y: Exit to title.</desc>
     <image>./leovigildo3.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20141103T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Leovigildo (part 3)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>leovigildo4.tap</path>
     <name>Leovigildo (part 4 - final)</name>
     <desc>The game is divided into 4 different blocks. The fourth block contains the ending sequence. You can watch it once you get a password for completing the third chapter. You can play each chapter freely, but you need to complete the third to access the ending sequence. You can get and carry boxes pressing DOWN, and drop them elsewhere pressing DOWN again. In every chapter you can use DOWN to get, examine, talk or use an object. You can manage your inventory pressing Z to change the cursor which points to the active slot to select which object you want to use / in which slot you want to store a new object. You can use two different keyboard configurations (WSADNM, QAOPM), Joystick Sinclair or Joystick Kempston. These are the key bindings, first for the WSADNM configuration, the the OPQAM configuration, then the Joystics. Controls: A, O, Left: go left; D, P, Right: go right.; S, A, Down: use object, examine, talk, get box, drop box.; N, Q, Up: jump.; M, Fire: Throw box (chapter 2); Z: select slot in the inventory; H: Pause; Y: Exit to title.</desc>
     <image>./leovigildo4.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20141103T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Leovigildo (part 4 - final)</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./lostinworlds.tap</path>
     <name>Lost In Worlds</name>
     <desc>Little platformer made with Platform Game Designer. Explore strange worlds and back home! Controls: O,P - Direction; SPACE - Jump.</desc>
     <image>./lostinworlds.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180612T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Nihirash</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Lost In Worlds</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./marianothedragon.tzx</path>
     <name>Mariano the Dragon: Capers in Cityland</name>
     <desc>A difficult mission is waiting for Mariano, the Pink Dragon. All his friends have been kept in prison by the evil "Tetrarca Pachin Poi Poi", on the planet called Cityland, for not having carried out the tasks assigned to them, and the only way for Mariano to get the keys from the cells is to perform these tasks.</desc>
     <image>./marianothedragon.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20080513T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Mariano the Dragon: Capers in Cityland</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./maritrinimonsterslayerp.tzx</path>
     <name>Maritrini Freelance Monster Slayer - Prequel</name>
     <desc>This game is a prequel to "Maritrini, Freelance Monster Slayer". Maritrini McAndrews, the famous actress with a starring role in "Maritrini, Monster Slayer", has a really flamboyant life, full of meetings and parties. One morning, she woke up to an amazing hangover, with her one night stand lying to her side, in her huge mansion located at the outskirts of the city. A bad "absentas night", some would say. She really has to hurry to get in time to an audition for "Vigorous Monsters with Shiny, Manly Chests", which she intended to be her next big success in the movies. The only solution is jumping to her car and drive away to the studios, but FIRST she must complete some... "basic morning tasks". Besides, there's a mad pig wandering around the house (George Clooney missed her pet in one of the latest huge parties!) which is a real bummer. And, besides, Maritrini and her one night stand passed out while watching "The Goonies" late at night in cable TV, and the mixture of absenta, cathodic rays, and sleep privation made the Fratelli Family corporeus... and really angry. Those are really bad guys! Can you help Maritrini to complete her "basic morning tasks"?</desc>
     <image>./maritrinimonsterslayerp.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20121004T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Maritrini Freelance Monster Slayer - Prequel</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./maritrinimonsterslayer.tzx</path>
     <name>Maritrini Freelance Monster Slayer</name>
     <desc>This is one of those games which simple and straight-forward mechanics: kill everything in sight, don't get lost, look for stamina-recharging bottles to fill-up and keys to open doors, destroy the enemy spawners (otherwise they will keep on respawning forever), look for the exit to the next level, write down the password in a book for writing down passwords, score tons of points, jump in the jumpin' jacks' trampoline, and stop reading magazines with naked women. Controls: O - left; P - right; Q - up, A - down, SPACE - shoot</desc>
     <image>./maritrinimonsterslayer.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20110817T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Maritrini Freelance Monster Slayer</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./miner.tap</path>
     <name>Miner'49er</name>
     <desc>The idea of the game is to collect all of the gold bags before your time runs out. As well you have to dodge the ghost of the dead miner that roams the caverns. They chase you and try to stop you getting the gold. Keys: O/P: left/right; M: climb; H: help. Good luck, you'll need it!</desc>
     <image>./miner.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170616T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Bootlegger</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Miner'49er</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./minesweeper16.tap</path>
     <name>Minesweeper 16</name>
     <desc>Minesweeper is a ZX Spectrum implementation of the classic Minesweeper puzzle, familiar to many people as one of the games bundled with Microsoft Windows. This is a 16K edition.</desc>
     <image>./minesweeper16.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Blerkotron</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Minesweeper 16 v1.0</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./minesweeper48.tap</path>
     <name>Minesweeper 48</name>
     <desc>Minesweeper is a ZX Spectrum implementation of the classic Minesweeper puzzle, familiar to many people as one of the games bundled with Microsoft Windows. This is a 48K edition. The 48K edition features more options (like the 'Heroes' mode where the boards are based on classic Speccy sprites).</desc>
     <image>./minesweeper48.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171201T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Blerkotron</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Minesweeper 48 v1.0</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./parachute.tzx</path>
     <name>Parachute</name>
     <desc>Our mission is to reach the base avoiding all the dangers that lie in wait for us: helicopters, birds, antiaircraft batteries, explosive balloons, guardians, traps, etc. You will be thrown in different scenarios and with the sole help of your parachute you will have to arrive safely at the end of your mission. You have Fuel, which helps you descend faster, but be careful, the fuel runs out, you must manage it wisely. In some places you can refuel. Luck! You will need it. Free conversion based on the Atari classic "Parachute".</desc>
     <image>./parachute.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180131T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Miguetelo</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Parachute</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./physiced.tap</path>
     <name>Physiced</name>
     <desc>A Physics Based Arcade Game in ZX Spectrum BASIC. The ball bounces under gravity, add momentum with direction keys to affect it's movement and guide it to the (green) exit. Featuring 20 levels of Teleporters, Switches, Score Bonuses, Score Penalties, Gravity Flips and very rudimentary graphics.  Cheat modes, and a level design tool included for anyone who wants to play with the code. Default Keys (re-definable) = Q,A,O,P; Cheat mode uses SYMBOL SHIFT on menu screen + letters.</desc>
     <image>./physiced.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170613T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Uglifruit</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Physiced</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./pilotattack.tap</path>
     <name>Pilot Attack</name>
     <desc>Horizontally scrolling shooter for Sinclair ZX Spectrum 48k home computer.</desc>
     <image>./pilotattack.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170729T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Misfit</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Pilot Attack [v.1.1]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./robotsrumble.tzx</path>
     <name>Robots Rumble</name>
     <desc>Somekind of arcade-puzzle-plataformer made with ADG. In this game you have to guide the robot to the latest screen of each planet and throw it into the lava. You control the robot with the right and left magnets. Avoid green radioactive rocks and guardians. You need to recharge your energy picking up the batteries. Keys: Q-A Up-Down left magnet. P-L Up-Down right magnet. Load in 128k for music.</desc>
     <image>./robotsrumble.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20180927T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Miguetelo</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Robots Rumble</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./snaked3.tap</path>
     <name>Snaked</name>
     <desc>A simple, but quite pacy (for ZX Spectrum Basic) Snake-a-like, that doesn't use any graphics as such. Instructions: Eat the purple things regularly, or else you'll starve. Don't eat yourself. Keys Q,A,O,P.</desc>
     <image>./snaked3.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170614T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Uglifruit</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Snaked</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game> 
   <game>
     <path>./snuffo.tap</path>
     <name>Snuffo</name>
     <desc>Play as Snuffo the clown, running round town murdering children. Can be loaded on any Spectrum emulator, or saved to cassette tape and loaded on a real machine. This is my first game, I was just messing around in CGD to see what I could make.</desc>
     <image>./snuffo.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171207T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Fadge Games</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Snuffo</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./spacejunk.tzx</path>
     <name>Space Junk</name>
     <desc>A strange signal has crossed the Solar System, damaging the mining bases that the human being has dispersed through space. All the robots and auxiliary machines have gone crazy and any object that approaches them will be considered as objective to eliminate. Your mission will be to destroy the six generators that power these machines at each base avoiding that they can overheat, explode and produce a chain reaction that could eliminate the Earth. Once finished your mission you will be able to return home. The enemies are indestructible, some of them may be paralyzed for a short period of time. Good luck!</desc>
     <image>./spacejunk.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171029T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Miguetelo</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Space Junk</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./speccysnake.z80</path>
     <name>Speccy-Snake</name>
     <desc>A simple Snake game for the ZX Spectrum.</desc>
     <image>./speccysnake.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20170804T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Retrojatekos</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Speccy-Snake [v.1.0T]</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./unhallowed.tap</path>
     <name>Unhallowed</name>
     <desc>It's Halloween and you're on your way home from work, tired and hungry and wanting nothing more than to put your feet up in front of the TV. But something dark and evil lurks within your home, waiting for you to return...</desc>
     <image>./unhallowed.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20181031T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Blerkotron</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Unhallowed 1.02</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
   <game>
     <path>./vallation128.tzx</path>
     <name>Vallation</name>
     <desc>Can you escape the pirate planet? Vallation is a stunning conversion of a C64 game originally produced by Jason Kelk (TMR / Cosine) and now presented on the ZX Spectrum by Tardis Remakes.  Featuring superb detailed graphics, quality soundtracks and lots of shoot 'em up action!  The Psytronik release is presented with incredible artwork by renowned industry artist Oliver Frey and features a specially enhanced 128K version with new AY soundtrack, a complete extra level with 49 new screens to blast your way through.</desc>
     <image>./vallation128.png</image>
     <rating>0</rating>
     <releasedate>20171114T000000</releasedate>
     <developer>Psytronik Software</developer>
     <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
     <genre>Vallation 128k</genre>
     <players>1</players>
   </game>
 </gameList>